thejapaneseshop.co.uk 2013-04-30

# Japanese Gift Ideas | Privacy Policy from The Japanese Shop

## About The Japanese Shop

This is the privacy policy of The Japanese Shop Limited (Company No. 6820799) Registered Office address; 43 Hookstone Road, Harrogate, North Yorkshire, HG2 8BT ("we", "us").

We are mindful of the importance of upholding the security of information under our control.  All data collected through the www.thejapaneseshop.co.uk website (the "Website") is stored on secure servers, and we have stringent security and confidentiality procedures covering the storage and disclosure of such information, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1988.  The following Privacy Policy forms part of our Terms and Conditions and will help you to understand how your personal information collected during your use of the Website will be treated by us.  If you have any queries on this please don't hesitate to contact us via the details set out at the end of this policy.

## Consent

We have a strong commitment towards the privacy of sensitive information.  This Privacy Policy sets out how we use personal information obtained about you during your use of the Website.  Your use of the Website signifies that you have given us your consent to such use of your data and your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

## What personal information do we collect?

We may collect personal information when you contact us or when you fill in a form on the Website, including without limitation if you register on the Website, place an order through the Website or report a problem with our Website.  We may also collect information regarding details of visits to our Website.  Any personal information we collect will be used by us strictly in accordance with current data protection legislation and this Privacy Policy. We will store the information we collect from you and hold it electronically or otherwise.

## IP Address & Cookies

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers.  This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

We use cookies to keep track of your information during the time you view the Website. We also use them to recognise return visitors and to track our promotions and projects. We gather this information for internal use only and will never authorise the release of this information with anyone outside of The Japanese Shop.

We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue without changing your settings, we'll assume that you are happy to receive all cookies on The Japanese Shop website. However, if you would like to, you can change your cookie settings at any time. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies.  However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the Website.  Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.

## Who do we share your information with?

We disclose information to employees for the purpose of operating the Website.  Unless you request otherwise, we may also share your details with select third parties for the purpose of marketing and promotional activities.  We may contact you for such marketing purposes by email or other electronic messages, post and/or fax (depending on the information we collect from you).

We will not sell your details to any third party.  If you do not wish for us to share your details with third parties, other than our employees, or if you do not wish to receive such offers then you can at any time write to us, or email us at the address in the "[Contact Us](http://www.thejapaneseshop.co.uk/pages/Contact-Us.html)".

## Your rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes and to ask us not to share your personal data with third parties other than our employees. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by contacting us at the address in the "Contact Us" section below.

You also have the right to see the personal data (as defined in the Data Protection Act 1988) that we keep about you, on receipt of a written request, verification of your identity, and payment of a fee of £10.  If you are concerned that any of the information we hold on you is incorrect or if you wish to object to the use we have made of your personal data, please contact us at the address in the "Contact Us" section below.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may modify our Privacy Policy from time to time in our sole discretion; if so, we will post a revised version of this Privacy Policy on this webpage.  We urge you to check the Privacy Policy regularly to obtain the most up to date copy.  Modifications will be effective when they are posted on the website.

## Other websites

From time to time our Website may contain links to and from other internet sites.  Please note that this Privacy Policy only covers this Website.  Any other website which is linked to or from this Website will have their own privacy policies, including without limitation the Global Innovation Network website, and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## Contact Us

If you have any comments or queries in connection with our Privacy Policy, please email [customerservice@thejapaneseshop.co.uk](mailto:customerservice@thejapaneseshop.co.uk) or write to;

The Japanese Shop Ltd  
The Studio  
Harrogate Business Centre  
Hookstone Avenue  
Harrogate  
HG2 8ER  
UK
